http://www.tools4boards.com/privacy.html

en / USD
Select regional settings:
Ethiopia
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Heard and McDonald Islands
Holy See (Vatican City State)
Virgin Islands, British
Virgin Islands, U.S.
Ethiopia
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Heard and McDonald Islands
Holy See (Vatican City State)
Virgin Islands, British
Virgin Islands, U.S.
Ethiopia
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Heard and McDonald Islands
Holy See (Vatican City State)
Virgin Islands, British
Virgin Islands, U.S.
Ethiopia
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Heard and McDonald Islands
Holy See (Vatican City State)
Virgin Islands, British
Virgin Islands, U.S.
0 items in cart
Subtotal:
Privacy
Tools4Boards Website Privacy PolicyThis statement discloses the privacy practices and policies for the Tools4Boards website. If you have any questions about these practices and policies, please contact us at:Tools4Boards3017 6St. SWCalgary, AB Canada T2S 2M1Tel: 403-243-5441Email: info@tools4boards.comTools4Boards respects your personal privacy. We believe ensuring the security of your personal information is an important part of our job. If we ask you to provide any personal information, we will tell you the purposes for which we intend to use that information. Your personal information is not sold to anyone for any purpose.Information Collection, Use and DisclosureInformation gathered on tools4boards.com falls under the following categories:Aggregate Site Use InformationCookies and Other TechnologiesSocial NetworkingThird party Analytics or Ad Serving ServicesOnline Order Information and Security Aggregate Site Use InformationWe record information about the pages viewed by all of our website visitors. This data includes internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, connection speed, read time, display time, and number of clicks. We use this data, in aggregate form, to compile statistics and reports for the use of Tools4Boards, and to improve the online experience for all visitors. We may, on occasion, provide portions of this aggregate information to vendors, consultants, potential advertisers, or news agencies. Typical uses of the data in this fashion would be to gauge the amount of interest in our site and/or to plan for site infrastructure improvements.Cookies and Other TechnologiesA cookie is a small text file stored on a user’s hard drive. Cookies are required to shop on our site. We also use cookies to assist with anonymous site traffic analysis, which includes tracking the time/date of visits, pages viewed, and referring URLs. We may use cookies to serve our remarketing campaigns so that third-party vendors, including Google and Facebook, show our ads on sites across the Internet. You can opt out of the third parties’ use of cookies by visiting their advertising preferences settings. We may also use web beacons or pixel tags to compile tracking information reports regarding website user demographics, website traffic patterns, and website purchases. None of the tracking information in these reports can be connected to the identities or other personal information of individual users. For our own research purposes we may link tracking information with personal information voluntarily provided by website users. Once such a link is made, all of the linked information is treated as personal information and will be used and disclosed only in accordance with this Privacy Policy.Social NetworkingWhen you use certain aspects of the Tools4Boards website or other services, or you post information to other social networking sites (e.g. posting a link to the Tools4Boards Facebook, Instagram or Twitter pages, or “liking” a product on your Facebook account, or “pinning” a product on your Pinterest account), the personal information that you post or share in connection with these third-party sites is visible to other persons and can be read, collected, used and disclosed by other persons. Any information provided to such third-party social networking sites and other sites is outside of the control of Tools4Boards and is not governed by this policy.Third Party Analytics or Ad Serving ServicesTools4Boards may use certain third-party analytics and/or ad serving services. The providers of these services may independently collect, use, and disclose your IP address together with information about your visits to this and other websites that they service in accordance with their own privacy policies (and not this privacy policy). These services may use their own cookies and other data collection technologies. They may use this information in order to improve your experience, to gain a view of how people are using websites that they service so that improvements can be made, and as otherwise permitted in their privacy policies. Tools4Boards may also use targeted advertising service providers to tailor Tools4Boards advertisements to your preferences. These advertisements may appear on the Tools4Boards website or social media sites, or on third party sites. If you have opted in to receive email news or offers, Tools4Boards may use your email address to target advertising to you. You may opt out of participating in these targeted ad programs by sending an email to info@tools4boards.com indicating you would like to opt out from Tools4Boards email newsletters.Online Order Information and SecurityIf you place an order online, we only require the information needed to complete the processing of your orders and billing. We also share our users’ personal information with outside shipping companies and credit card processing companies in order to bill and ship your order, but we do not provide any more information than necessary for these purposes. We may also use the information to contact you regarding your order.Our Site SecurityWe use appropriate security safeguards to protect your personal information against loss, theft, and unauthorized access. Any personal information you provide to Tools4Boards in connection with a product order is exchanged on a secure server. We use one of today’s most advanced security systems, the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol, to encrypt, or encode, information you send to us in the order process. The encryption process protects information, such as your credit card number, and billing and shipping information by scrambling it before it is sent from your computer. Only once we receive your information is it decoded, and we make all reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our own systems.Warning:E-mail is not a secure means to send personal information, as it is not encrypted. We strongly encourage you to use our secure ordering process when ordering online.International TransfersWe may transfer your personal information across provincial or national borders to fulfill any of the purposes in this policy or in the Tools4Boards Privacy Code, including to service providers located outside of Canada who may be subject to applicable disclosure laws in those jurisdictions.Opting OutIf you wish to have any of your personal information removed from our databases, or if you no longer want us to send any further communications to you, please send an e-mail to info@tools4boards.com. Please note, however, that as a business we are required by law to maintain certain information about our customers, as noted above in Information, Collection, Use & Disclosure, which we are required by law to maintain even after a customer has opted out of receiving further communications.Email SubscriptionTools4Boards newsletters are sent only to users who opt in. Our subscriber database is never sold, rented or loaned to any other parties. Subscribers wishing to update their contact information, or opt out of receiving emails are able to do so by sending an email to info@tools4boards.com . From time to time, Tools4Boards may send you safety notices or recalls related to products you have purchased. We collect aggregate information regarding open rates, page views, and generated sales from our HTML email newsletters. Aggregate information does not personally identify individuals. Subscribers concerned about collection of aggregate information may unsubscribe by sending an email to info@tools4boards.com .Fraud PreventionTools4Boards reserves the right to co-operate with local, national, or international law enforcement or other authorities in the investigation of improper or unlawful activities and this may require the disclosure of personal information. If such an investigation requires disclosure of personal information kept in our records, we may be required by law to cooperate. We also reserve the right to report improper or unlawful user activities on our site, which may require the disclosure of personal information relating to those individuals conducting such improper or unlawful activities. There may also be other circumstances under which Tools4Boards is required by law to disclose personal information.PurposesIn addition to the above purposes, Tools4Boards collects individual’s personal information for the following reasons:To provide retail services and process customer purchases;To understand the product and service needs of our customers and prospective customers;To develop and manage products and services to meet the needs of our customers;To contact individuals directly for products and services that may be of interest;To meet regulatory requirements;To ensure a high standard of service to our customers;To verify a customer’s identity.Customer Purchases: When customers purchase an item(s) through our website we only request the information needed to complete the processing of orders and billing.We may share our customers’ personal information with outside shipping companies and credit card processing companies in order to bill and ship orders, but we do not provide any more information than necessary for these purposes.We may also use the information to contact customers regarding orders or to provide customers with future information about our products and services.We use information on purchases to compile statistics and reports for the use of Tools4Boards.We analyze aggregated information to understand our customers and their needs.LinksThis web site contains links to other sites and advertisements. This privacy statement only applies to information collected by our web site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices and policies of these third parties.Accuracy of InformationWe strive to ensure that any personal information we retain and use is as accurate, complete and up-to-date as necessary for the purposes for which we will use it. We do not routinely update personal information unless necessary for these purposes. Nonetheless, if our records regarding your personal information are inaccurate or incomplete, we will amend that information at your request.Access To InformationAt your request, we will provide to you a statement explaining the extent to which we hold personal information about you, and we will explain how that information has been used or disclosed by us. This page will be updated if information about the collection and use of your personal data changes.IOS APP Location-Based ServicesTo provide location-based services through the mobile application, Tools4Boards and our partners and licensees may collect, use, and share precise location data, including the real-time geographic location of your mobile device. This location data is collected anonymously in a form that does not personally identify you and is used by Tools4Boards and our partners and licensees to provide and improve location-based products and services.Some location-based services offered by Tools4Boards, such as the “MultiCurrency” Feature displaying product prices in the customers’ (or potential customers’) local currency and location-based Push Notifications, require your personal information for the feature to work.IOS APP Push NotificationsPush Notifications are sent only to users who have chosen to opt into receiving such notifications. Mobile application users who do not wish to receive Push Notifications may opt out by disabling Push Notifications within the Apple iOS settings, or by disabling specific notification topics from within this mobile application in the Account > Push Notification section.Changes To This Privacy PolicyTools4Boards may update this privacy policy in the future. We will notify you about material changes to this privacy policy by placing a prominent notice on our website. As well, a history of those changes will be noted here, beginning with changes published after April 30, 2018.Any changes in our use of personal information contrary to Customers’ initial consent will be posted, in advance, on our website with instructions regarding consent to any changes. Notices may also be sent by email. All changes will remain in compliance with federal and provincial privacy legislation.
Sign up for Tools4Boards news
Email
*
Subscribe
Can't subscribe you right now. Try later
Thank you for subscribing to the newsletter! We hope you enjoy shopping at Tools4Boards
Contact us
629 James Mckevitt Road SW, Calgary, AB, CA, T2Y2E7
1-877-4-SKIWAX (1-877-475-4929)
© 1990 - 2020 Tools4Boards. All rights reserved.
Powered by X-Cart
